<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dather</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="title_activity_terms_of_use">TermsOfUseActivity</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="infoText">
        <![CDATA[
            <h1>TRINITY COLLEGE DUBLIN</h1>
            <h1>INFORMATION SHEET FOR PROSPECTIVE PARTICIPANTS</h1>
            <p>A research to identify and analyze influences on the learning quality of writing computer software.</p>
<br>
            <h2>Context of research</h2>
            <p>Learning how to program and thinking like a programmer can be a very different process for different people. It seems that some students have more problems and struggles than others.
            Also more experienced programmers sometimes write better code and sometimes create less quality.
            This dissertation investigates metrics of environmental influences in the cognitive processes which are responsible for the code quality and performance in the process of software developing.
            The programming skills are measured by automated code analysis software and then correlated with gathered data during the development process.
            The built in sensors and of the participants mobile phone such as the location, microphone, accelerometers etc. are being used to gather information about the environment and context.
            Therefore it is required for the participants to install and start the provided android application on their device.</p>
<br>
            <h2>Benefits for the participants</h2>
            <p>The participants will get feedback and information about their individual results and the code quality compared to other participants. They can also request the results of this study and
            the influencing factors in the quality of the results. This knowledge can help to increase their own code quality and optimise their working environment.</p>
<br>
            <h2>The procedure of this study</h2>
            <p>Each participant needs to install the data gathering application on their cellular devices and give the permissions to collect the relevant data. Before the participation on the programming task, the participant needs to start the data gathering in the app.
            After completing the task, the participants need to submit the solution and need to answer some additional questions through the application.
            Analyzing the metrics correlations with the code requires that the participant has a Github account and grant access to the working repository.</p>
<br>
            <h2>The expected duration of the participants involvement</h2>
            <p>First, the participant needs to download the app and initially enter information about person, university and experience. Before starting the
            programming task, the student needs to open the application and log the start time. After the submission the app asks the participant additional occasional questions. The estimated time for
            the work on the programming assignment including the submission and setup is not more than 3 hours.</p>
<br>
            <h2>Usage of gathered data</h2>
            <p>The data is exclusively used to for this study and will not be provided to anyone else then the research team.
            The collected data during the study will be anonymized and the transmission over the internet will exclusively be in an encrypted form and just used for statistical analysis purpose. The data will also  be stored encrypted and a not traceable identifier will be used to keep the data anonymous.
            Participants can be assured they will not be mentioned by name or any other unique identifier and their data will be handled with the most possible discretion.
            We also guarantee no direct quotations and contextual appropriateness.</p>
<br>
            <h2>Rights of the participant</h2>
            Every participant has the right to withdraw and to omit the individual collected data, without penalty.
            A requested withdraw would  lead to deletion of the entire data of the participant which was collected related to that study.
            Participants also have the provision to receive an individual debriefing after participation.
            The participant has the right to request a digital copy of the dissertation after its completion.</p>
        ]]>
"</string>
    <string name="title_activity_rec">RecActivity</string>
</resources>
